profitwell.com 2018-08-15

# ProfitWell

Our lawyers made the below nice and legal (because that's their job). They did let us put together this summary though, which let's us boil down everything you're about to read in a nice, easy to understand context. Do your dilligence on the below though (that's your job). If anything doesn't make sense or you'd like to put together custom terms, email us at [product@profitwell.com.](mailto:product@profitwell.com). For most companies we're happy to oblige to fulfill your security, compliance, and privacy requirements. 

##### We do not and will not sell your data

To be crystal clear - **_ProfitWell does not and will not ever sell your data to third parties. Your data is your data._** Further, your data is rarely accessed with the only reasons we'd ever look at your data is if there's a QA or security issue, or if you give us permission for the purposes of analysis and helping you with identifying problems/opportunities in your business. 

We do study data in aggregate to improve our products, security, and knowledge of the market to help you. If you'd like to opt out of this, you can through signing a custom Terms of Use with us. Just email [product@profitwell.com.](mailto:product@profitwell.com) to get the ball rolling.

How do we make money then? Well, we do this by showing you problems and opportunities in your business through the free metrics and then sell you tools to solve those problems automatically for you. We think that's just a better way of doing business, because selling you graphs (although they're beautiful and insightful) just doesn't feel right. 

##### What about GDPR and EU data protection?

We have you all taken care of on the GDPR front. You can check out more information our GDPR practices on our [GDPR and EU specific page](https://www.profitwell.com/gdpr?hsLang=en-us), but you can also sign our [Data Processing Addendum here](https://na2.docusign.net/Member/PowerFormSigning.aspx?PowerFormId=e0f7bd18-e8cc-480d-a3d3-b54bece12bf9&__hssc=174954301.6.1526964607842&__hstc=174954301.6fb8d0dd1ce0500a929f70c1320557df.1523498660889.1525812099390.1526964607842.19&__hsfp=696778910&hsCtaTracking=f03e30da-f630-4d1e-bbd4-7033fbda9234%7Cc600ff9f-816f-43b4-be7d-966375843451). We're also fully certified under the US-EU and US-Swiss Privacy Shield, which you can learn more about below. 

##### How's ProfitWell's security?

When it comes to security we do _a lot_ , from CCTV and personnel trainings to penetration testing and network defenses this is an area that's extremely important to our continued success. There's a full write up here on our security page, but if you'd like our full security risk assessment, send us an email at [product@profitwell.com.](mailto:product@profitwell.com)

##### Effective: 05/22/2018

This Privacy Policy applies to the websites: www.priceintelligently.com, www.profitwell.com, and www.saasfest.io (the “Sites”) owned and operated by 200 OK, LLC (collectively, “ProfitWell”, “we”, “us”, or “our”). This Privacy Policy describes how ProfitWell collects, uses, shares and secures the personal information you provide, as well as the human resources data transferred to us for processing on behalf of our customers. It also describes your choices regarding use, access and correction of your personal information. 

##### EU-U.S. and Swiss-U.S. Privacy Shield Frameworks

200 OK, LLC complies with the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework and Swiss-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information transferred from the European Union and Switzerland to the United States. 200 OK, LLC has certified to the Department of Commerce that it adheres to the Privacy Shield Principles. If there is any conflict between the terms in this privacy policy and the Privacy Shield Principles, the Privacy Shield Principles shall govern. To learn more about the Privacy Shield program, and to view our certification, please visit https://www.privacyshield.gov/. 

ProfitWell is responsible for the processing of personal data it receives, under each Privacy Shield Framework, and subsequently transfers to a third party acting as an agent on its behalf. ProfitWell complies with the Privacy Shield Principles for all onward transfers of personal data from the EU and Switzerland, including the onward transfer liability provisions. 

With respect to personal data received or transferred pursuant to the Privacy Shield Frameworks, ProfitWell is subject to the regulatory enforcement powers of the U.S. Federal Trade Commission. In certain situations, ProfitWell may be required to disclose personal data in response to lawful requests by public authorities, including to meet national security or law enforcement requirements. 

In compliance with the Privacy Shield Principles, 200 OK, LLC commits to resolve complaints about our collection or use of your personal information. EU and Swiss individuals with inquiries or complaints regarding our Privacy Shield policy should first contact 200 OK, LLC at: 

Patrick Campbell, CEO, patrick@profitwell.com. 

200 OK, LLC has further committed to refer unresolved Privacy Shield complaints to an alternative dispute resolution provider located in the United States. If you do not receive timely acknowledgment of your complaint from us, or if we have not addressed your complaint to your satisfaction, you may visit https://www.jamsadr.com/eu-us-privacy-shield for more information or to file a complaint (free of charge). 

To facilitate fast and convenient resolution of complaints, you agree to participate in on-line dispute resolution through JAMS Online Mediation (Endispute). 

Under certain conditions, Privacy Shield provides the right to invoke binding arbitration when other dispute resolution procedures have not provided resolution. [This is described in Annex I to the Privacy Shield.](https://www.privacyshield.gov/article?id=ANNEX-I-introduction)

##### Collection:

We may collect the following personal information from you: 

  * Contact Information, such as name, email address, mailing address, or phone number;
  * Demographic information, such as age, education, gender, interests and zip code;
  * Billing Information, such as credit card number and billing address; 
  * Unique Identifiers, such as username, account number or password;
  * Geo location based on IP address;
  * Information about your business, such as company name, company size, business type.

We may also collect, from you, personal information about your contacts such as Name and email address where we can send receipts of your purchases. When you provide us with personal information about your contacts we will only use this information for the specific reason for which it is provided. If you believe that one of your contacts has provided us with your personal information and you would like to request that it be removed from our database, please contact us at the contact information below. 

As is true of most websites, we gather certain information automatically. This information may include Internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, the files viewed on our site (e.g., HTML pages, graphics, etc.), operating system, date/time stamp, and/or clickstream data to analyze trends in the aggregate and administer the site. 

ProfitWell and its partners use cookies or similar technologies to analyze trends, administer the website, track users’ movements around the website, and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. You can control the use of cookies at the individual browser level, but if you choose to disable cookies, it may limit your use of certain features or functions on our website or service. 

##### Use:

The personal information as indicated being collected above is used for billing, identification, authentication, service improvement, research, and contact. 

##### Information Sharing

1\. With Third Parties: 

We may share your information with third-party business partners, for instance, for the purpose of enhancing our products and services. If you do not want us to share your personal information with these companies, contact us at the contact information below. 

2\. With Service Providers: 

We may share your information with third parties who provide services on our behalf to help with our business activities. These companies are authorized to use your personal information only as necessary to provide these services to us, to which these services may include: 

  * Payment processing
  * Providing customer service
  * Sending marketing communications
  * Conducting research and analysis
  * Providing cloud computing infrastructure

3\. With Public Authorities or Law Enforcement: 

In certain situations, ProfitWell may be required to disclose personal data in response to lawful requests by public authorities, including to meet national security or law enforcement requirements. We may also disclose your personal information as required by law, such as to comply with a subpoena or other legal process, when we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, when we believe there is a violation to our Terms of Service (see ProfitWell Terms of Service), protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or respond to a government request. If ProfitWell is involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our website, of any change in ownership, uses of your personal information, and choices you may have regarding your personal information. We do not sell, rent or share personal information with third parties without your prior consent. 

##### Security

The security of your personal information is important to us. We follow generally accepted standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once it is received. 200 OK, LLC ensures that all source code, files and data remain private and confidential. Due to the sensitive nature of source code we take this very seriously and make it our primary concern for all customers. We restrict access to personal information to ProfitWell employees, contractors and agents who need to know that information in order to operate, develop, or improve our service. These individuals are bound by confidentiality obligations and may be subject to discipline, including termination and criminal prosecution, if they fail to meet these obligations. 

If you have any questions about the security of your personal information, you can contact us at the contact information below. We may retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services, comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes and enforce our agreements. 

##### Access

Upon request ProfitWell will provide you with information about whether we hold any of your personal information. You may access, correct, or request deletion of your personal information by logging into your account or by contacting us at the contact information below. We will respond to your request within a reasonable timeframe. In certain circumstances we may be required by law to retain your personal information, or may need to retain your personal information in order to continue providing a service. 

200 OK, LLC acknowledges that you have the right to access your personal information. ProfitWell has no direct relationship with the individuals whose personal data it processes. An individual who seeks access, or who seeks to correct, amend, or delete inaccurate data should direct their query to the 200 OK, LLC’s Client (the data controller). If requested to remove data we will respond within a reasonable timeframe. In certain circumstances we may be required by law to retain your personal information, or may need to retain your personal information in order to continue providing a service. 

##### Choice

We partner with a third party to display advertising on our website or to manage our advertising on other sites. Our third party partner may use cookies or similar technologies in order to provide you advertising based upon your browsing activities and interests. If you wish to opt out of interest-based advertising click [here](http://preferences-mgr.truste.com/) (or if located in the European Union click [here](http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/)). Please note you will continue to receive generic ads. 

You may sign-up to receive email or newsletter or other communications from us. If you would like to discontinue receiving this information, you may update your email preferences by using the “Unsubscribe” link found in emails we send to you or by contacting us at the contact information below. 

##### Changes to This Privacy Policy

We may update this Privacy Policy to reflect changes to our information practices. If we make any material changes we will notify you by email (sent to the e-mail address specified in your account) or by means of a notice on this website prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices. 

##### Privacy Questions / Feedback

If you have questions or concerns about ProfitWell’s Privacy Policy please contact us at [product@profitwell.com](mailto:product@profitwell.com) or 109 Kingston Street (Fourth Floor), Boston, MA 02111.
